原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译            冰岛豆腐    @少年影视派
翻译             feip    蛇蝎再续前缘栗
翻译              建峤    布塔
校对            冰岛豆腐
时间轴          冰岛豆腐 Jenny
后期              咖啡・Lee
总监             冰岛豆腐
《致命女人》前情提要
Previously on Why Women Kill...
我以前弹钢琴
I used to play the piano.
-你还弹吗  -我丈夫不喜欢我弹琴
- Do you still play? - My husband didn't care for my playing.
我们的女儿因我而死
Our daughter died because of me.
闯祸的是我
I'm the one who's responsible.
看起来我只剩六个月的时间了
It seems I only have six months to live.
六个月
Six months!
我想着一刀两断更好...
I thought a clean break was just better for...
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
他单膝跪地  问我愿不愿意嫁给他
He got down on one knee and asked me if I would marry him.
他说他的婚姻就快结束了
He told me that his marriage is ending.
他说只要再给他六个月的时间就行
He said he just needs six months.
六个月
Six months.
你知道你丈夫是同性恋吗
Do you know your husband's a homosexual?
他也患上了在同性恋男子群体中肆虐的那种疾病
He has that new disease that all the gay men are spreading.
你在说谎
That's a lie.
他是我丈夫见过的第三位患者
He's the third man my husband's seen who's had it.
前两个都已经死了
The first two are dead.
你需要关照
You need care.
你觉得我会在这种时候离开你
Karl, you think I'd leave you at a time like this?
取消旅行
Cancel the trip?
这不公平
That's not fair.
这本应是我这辈子最棒的一个夏天
This was supposed to be the best summer of my life.
这也可能是卡尔一生里最后一个夏天
And this could be the last summer of Karl's life,
所以拜托别生气了
so please stop sulking.
我的儿子到底怎么了
What's happened to my boy?
汤米出车祸了
Tommy's been in a car accident.
不得不缝了几针
He needed some stitches.
这是什么鬼
What in the world?
那是文身吗
Is that a tattoo?
以后情变了肯定会后悔的
One of these days he'll regret that.
她也会后悔的
So will she.
-哇  -看到了吧
- Oh. Wow. - Right?
-你给我买了一辆车  -我说了我会照顾你的
- You bought me a car? - I said I would take care of you.
你不能把车退掉  车不是你的
You can't return the car. It's not yours.
但他是因为嗑药嗑疯了才买的
Yeah, but he's coked out of his mind.
接受一个这种情况下男人送的礼物  "吃相"可不太好看
To accept a gift from a man in that condition is not a good look.
-钥匙给我  -够了
- Just give me the keys. - Stop it.
上楼  收拾你的东西
Go upstairs, get your stuff!
我要你立刻离开我家
I want you out of my house now!
想得美
That's not gonna happen.
我能帮上你什么忙
How can I help?
把你知道的关于洁德的一切都告诉我
Tell me everything you know about Jade.
首先  那不是她的真名
Well, for starters, that's not her real name.
致命女人
第一季 第九集
我叫艾米莉・斯坦顿
My name is Emily Stanton.
我在两年多前去世
I was killed over two years ago,
但我妈妈还是会每天都想着我
but my mama still thinks about me every day.
就连她涂口红的时候
Even when she's just putting on lipstick,
她也会突然想起她有多爱我
she'll suddenly remember how much she loved me.
我从天堂上俯视着妈妈
I look down on Mama from heaven.
我看着她因为我担心她
I watch her because I'm worried about her.
她不幸福
She's not happy,
但爸爸不知道
but Daddy doesn't know
因为她总是在微笑
because she keeps smiling.
妈妈很生他的气
Mama is very angry with him,
我有预感她会做出很可怕的事
and I have a feeling that she's gonna do something awful.
你今天有什么计划
So, what have you got planned for the day?
没什么
Oh, nothing much.
我会和一个新朋友聚会
I'll be spending time with a new friend.
是吗  她叫什么
Oh? What's her name?
琼恩[六月]
June.
我感觉你会很喜欢她
I have a feeling you'd really like her.
你们俩要做什么
And what are you two doing?
我会开车送她去看医生
I offered to drive her to a doctor's appointment,
但这只不过是
but that's really just an excuse
我想找她谈她在交往的那男人的借口
for me to talk to her about the man she's seeing.
为什么
Why?
我不赞同这段关系
I don't approve of the relationship,
所以我决定让他们分手
so I've decided to break them up.
贝丝・安  这可不好
Beth Ann, that's not nice.
也许吧
Maybe not,
但很有必要
but it's necessary.
我叫艾德蒙・哈特
My name is Edmund Harte.
我去世的时候57岁
I was 57 when I died.
我的贱老婆就这么成了寡妇
That's how my bitch wife became my widow.
我时不时地会来看看我儿子怎么样
I check in from time to time to see how my kid is doing
因为我很担心他
'cause I'm worried about him.
他妈妈竭力想要控制他
His mother is desperate to control him,
但汤米是大人了
but Tommy's a man now,
可以自己做决定
able to make his own choices.
我知道娜奥米会随时随地
And I know Naomi is going to fight him
和他抗争
every step of the way.
祝你好运  孩子
Good luck, kid.
我可怜的孩子
My poor baby.
萨蒙妮
Simone?
不  是我
No, it's me.
妈  天呐
Mom. Oh, God.
没事  我什么都知道了
It's okay, I know everything.
你不用再保护她
You don't have to protect her anymore.
我也不生气
And I am not angry,
至少不生你的气
not at you anyway.
哈特夫人
Mrs. Harte?
院长来了
The hospital administrator has arrived.
谢谢
Ah, thank you.
科恩先生  谢谢你同意见我
Mr. Kern, thank you so much for agreeing to see me.
有何贵干  哈特夫人
How can I help you, Ms. Harte?
你认识萨蒙妮・格罗夫吗
Do you happen to know Simone Grove?
认识  她是我们医院最大的募捐者之一
I do. She's one of our hospital's biggest fundraisers.
对  在举办慈善晚宴之间
Yes. Well, in between benefit galas,
似乎萨蒙妮在性骚扰我儿子
it seems that Simone has been molesting my son,
可能已经多年了
possibly for years.
如果你允许她来探视或者给他打电话
If you allow her to visit or even phone him,
我就告你们医院  最后我会赢的
I will sue this hospital and I will win.
明白吗
Do you understand?
明白  我很抱歉
Yes. Um, I'm-I'm so sorry.
请放心  我们会极端慎重处理
Rest assured, this matter will be handled
这一问题
with the utmost discretion.
不用因为我而慎重
No need to be discreet on my account.
我打算告诉全镇的人
I intend on telling everyone in this town
这女人对我家做了什么
what that woman has done to my family.
领带不错
Nice tie.
我叫弗娜・罗伊
My name is Verna Roy.
32岁的时候我死于一场火灾
I was 32 when I died in a fire.
当时
At the time,
我是这里这个女孩的养母
I was a foster mother to this one right here.
我不喜欢说活人的坏话
I don't like to talk bad about the living,
但这个孩子真是坏透了
but this gal's pure poison.
我看到她现在住在
I can see she's now living
有着各种精美家具的豪宅里
in a fancy house with pretty things.
这意味着已经有男人被她迷住了
That means some man has fallen for her act.
伊莱  你要迟到了
Eli, you're gonna be late!
这个愚蠢的家伙
Stupid son of a bitch.
他可不知道她的能耐
He don't know what she's capable of,
但是我有预感他马上就要发现了
but I got a feeling he's about to find out.
你今天的动作有点迟钝
Moving kind of slow today.
你昨晚给我吃了什么  马用镇静剂吗
What did you give me last night, a horse tranquilizer?
如果你能在晚上十点以后就别再吸食
Well, I wouldn't have to give you anything
我当然不会让你吃任何东西了
if you'd stop doing coke after 10:00.
你说得我好像有自制力似的
You talk like I have self-control.
你都要让我觉得尴尬了
I'm almost embarrassed for you.
随便吧  快看
Well, whatever. Here, look.
我给你准备了惊喜
I've got a surprise.
有什么特别的事情吗
Whoa. What's the occasion?
今天是斯科塞斯日
It's Scorsese day.
听着  只是一个会议而已
Oh, look, it's just a meeting.
我觉得能让他导演我电影的可能性
I mean, the odds of him directing my movie
大概是一百万分之一吧
are, like, a million to one.
他很喜欢你的剧本  我想这是件大事
He loved your script. I think that's a big deal.
天哪  我只希望能在10点前清醒过来
God, I just-- I hope I can burn this off by 10:00.
我现在感觉很不在状态
I feel so out of it.
那你走运了
Well, luckily for you,
我知道如何准备"营养均衡"的一餐
I know how to prepare a well-balanced meal.
你把我照顾得太好了
Mmm. You take such good care of me.
斯科塞斯会执导你的电影的  我确信
Scorsese's gonna direct your movie, I know it,
而且会非常成功  我们会变得无比富有
and it's gonna be a big hit and we are going to be so rich.
借你吉言
From your lips...
我就知道有天我会遇到非常令人激动的事
I always knew something exciting would happen to me one day.
我想就是这事了
I think this is it.
再说一次  真的只是一个会议
Again, all right, it's just a meeting.
我一点都不担心
I'm not worried.
今年我的梦想都会实现
This is the year where all my dreams come true.
你好  珍妮
Hello, Jenny.
格罗夫夫妇
Oh, Mr. And Mrs. Grove.
请告诉我你们今晚有嫩煎小牛肉片
Please tell me you have the veal piccata tonight.
就是能吃到这口美味的想法让我今天精神饱满
Just the thought of it has kept me going all day.
很抱歉  我无法为两位安排座位
I'm sorry, but I can't seat you.
你们不是又客满了吧
Oh... oh, you're not overbooked again?
我看见我们常坐的桌子是空的
Well, I see our usual table is empty.
我不知道你把它订给谁了
I don't know who you promised it to,
但他们应该早点来的
but they should have gotten here sooner.
请坐  亲爱的
Here we are, my darling.
谢谢
Thank you.
-好了  -不管如何
- There we go. - Anyway,
我一直想找医院里的汤米
I've been trying to talk to Tommy in the hospital,
但是我却总也联系不到他
but I can't seem to get through to him.
真奇怪
It's bizarre.
抱歉  亲爱的  是我的幻觉
Sorry, darling, is it my imagination,
还是真的大家都在看我们
or are people staring at us?
我今天穿的可是纪梵希
I'm wearing Givenchy.
我穿纪梵希的时候人们总会盯着我看
They always stare when I wear Givenchy.
不是  我觉得他们只是在盯着我看
No, no, I think, actually, they're just staring at me.
你说得没错
You're right.
肯定是因为你的外套
It must be your jacket.
我跟你说过格子花呢过时了
I told you plaid is over.
格罗夫夫妇
Mr. And Mrs. Grove.
亨利  见到你真高兴
Oh, Henry, how lovely to see you.
真的非常抱歉  但恐怕
I'm terribly sorry, but I'm afraid
我不得不请两位离开
I have to ask you to leave.
上帝啊  他可以把外套脱掉的
Oh, for God's sake, he can take the jacket off.
怎么回事
What's wrong?
应该有人通知过你们了
Someone should have notified you.
两位在俱乐部的会员资格被取消了
Your membership to the club has been revoked.
开玩笑的吧
You can't be serious.
委员会下午召开了会议  投票是一致通过的
The committee met this afternoon. The vote was unanimous.
我们...我们在这家俱乐部15年了
W... We've belonged to this club for 15 years.
为什么你们要把我们踢出去
Why on earth would you want to kick us out?
因为我生病了  对不对
It's because I'm ill, isn't it?
我们需要保护自己的会员
We have to protect our members.
这种病是通过性传播的
It's a sexually transmitted disease.
共用网球场是不会传染的
You don't get it by sharing a fucking tennis court.
无论如何  两位的会员合约里有道德条款
All the same, your membership contract has a morals clause.
这里这么多的人
Of all the people here,
你觉得没道德的是我们
you think we're the ones who lack morals?
那边的梅森・里德吸食海洛因成瘾
Mason Reed over there is addicted to heroin,
苏珊・保罗在跟自己的姐夫上床
and Susan Paul is sleeping with her brother-in-law.
你更不想知道俱乐部的桑拿房里会发生什么
And you don't want to know what happens in the club sauna.
你这是在帮倒忙
That's not helpful.
我最后说一遍  格罗夫夫妇  请离开
For the last time, Mr. And Mrs. Grove, please go.
走吧
Shall we?
不知道您介不介意
Would you mind terribly...
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
再见  亨利
Goodbye, Henry.
真有你的  亲爱的
Good for you, dear.
别担心  亨利  我的我会喝掉
Oh, don't worry, Henry, I'm gonna drink mine.
再次感谢你给我推荐的产科医师
Thank you again for recommending this obstetrician.
我跟他电话里聊过了  感觉他很棒
I talked to him on the phone, he sounds wonderful.
希拉
Sheila?
你在想什么呢
What are you thinking about?
你接下来的婚礼
Uh, your upcoming wedding.
为我感到高兴吗
You excited for me?
是的
I am.
我很好奇
I'm curious,
你们有机会讨论过罗伯的期待吗
have you had a chance to discuss Rob's expectations?
-期待  -你想要一份事业
- Expectations? - Well, you want a career.
有的男人不允许自己的妻子去工作
Some men don't allow their wives to work.
罗伯知道我想成为一个歌手
Oh, well, Rob knows I want to be a singer.
我们谈过很多的
We've talked about it a lot.
自从你怀孕后吗
Since you've become pregnant?
这个嘛
Well...
没有
no.
或许是时候该谈谈了
Might be time for a chat.
罗伯给我感觉
Rob strikes me as the kind of man
会比较喜欢妻子待在家里
who'd prefer his wife to stay home.
你说得好像你认识他似的
You talk like you know him.
我了解他这种类型的男人
Oh, I know his type.
有钱  成功
Rich, successful.
那种男人想要的是一个堂下妻
That kind of man wants his wife in the kitchen,
喂饱孩子  给他倒马提尼
feeding the kids and pouring his martini.
罗伯才不是那样
Rob's not like that.
你绝对确定吗
You absolutely sure?
他最好能接受
Well, he better be okay with it,
否则我们之间就有问题了
or we're gonna have a problem.
我也是这么想的
That's what I was thinking.
根据这个  我们要找203号套房
Okay, according to this, we're looking for Suite 203.
希拉
Sheila.
来了
Coming!
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  我只是  非常紧张
Yeah, man, I'm sorry, I'm just, I'm really nervous.
我基本是看斯科塞斯的电影长大的
You know, I basically grew up on Scorsese movies.
兄弟  帮我个忙
Hey, buddy, do me a favor.
我希望我们在进去之前  你能调一下你的期望值
I want you to manage your expectations before we walk in here.
该死的  为什么  他是个混蛋吗
Shit. Why? Is he an asshole?
这么说吧  这不会是你期望的那场会议
Let's just say it isn't gonna be the meeting you were hoping for.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
你好  伊莱
Hello, Eli.
所以我从一开始就不会见到斯科塞斯吗
So I was never meeting Scorsese?
抱歉  你真的得仔细听听她要说的话
Sorry. You really need to hear her out.
为什么
Why?
这是什么狗屁干预行为吗
Is this some sort of bullshit intervention?
差不多吧
Something like that.
我去弄些咖啡
I'm gonna go get some coffee.
你想来一杯吗
You want a cup?
不用  好吧  好吧
No. Cool. Cool.
这太羞辱人了
Well, this is humiliating.
伊莱  那不是我的本意
Eli, that wasn't my intention.
但我们需要谈谈  私下里谈
But we need to talk. Privately.
谈什么
About?
艾琳・塔巴切尼克
Irene Tabatchnick.
艾琳・塔巴切尼克是他妈谁啊
Who the hell's Irene Tabatchnick?
睡在我们床上的那个女人
The woman who's been sleeping in our bed.
你最好坐下来  仔细听听剩下的部分
You may want to sit down for the rest of this.
如果本奈特医生的妻子把这事传了出去
If Dr. Bennett's wife told people,
那就违反了医患保密协议
that is a violation of doctor-patient confidentiality.
我们可以吊销他的行医执照
We should have his license revoked.
我们想在这事上耗费多少精力啊
How much energy do we really want to devote to all this?
这是歧视  我们必须反击
This is discrimination. We have to fight back.
然后为我的性生活和我的疾病引来更多注意力吗
And draw more attention to my sex life and my disease?
你不觉得大家会同情你吗
You don't think people will be sympathetic?
恰恰相反
On the contrary.
我觉得情况在好起来前只会先糟糕透顶
I think the situation's going to get much worse before it gets better.
那我们就别老想着这事了
Well, we won't dwell on it.
你不如先好好泡个热水澡吧
Why don't you take a nice, long, hot bath?
你似乎很疲惫
You seem exhausted.
原来被共和党人避之不及
Turns out being shunned by Republicans
会让人心力交瘁
takes rather a lot out of a person.
娜奥米  我一直想联系你呢
Naomi, I've been trying to reach you.
汤米怎么样了
How's Tommy?
他没事
He's fine.
我给医院打了好多次电话
Well, I keep calling the hospital,
但似乎一直都打不通
but I can never seem to get through.
这包里装的是什么
What are in the bags?
礼物
Ah, presents.
送我的吗
For me?
不  是你送的
No, from you.
你送我的每一份礼物  我现在都还给你
Every gift you ever gave me, I'm returning them.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你在巴伐利亚给我买的可爱的小雕像
This lovely figurine you got me while you were in Bavaria.
我现在不想要了
I don't want it anymore.
什么鬼
What the hell?!
以及这个可爱的银制音乐盒
Or this sweet silver music box.
我也不需要这个了
I don't need that either.
你是疯了吗
Have you lost your mind?
是的  因为我知道了你对我儿子做的事
I have, because I know what you did to my son.
你要说的就这么一句叹息吗
That's all you have to say?
我理解你的愤怒
I-I understand your anger,
但如果你能给我个机会解释...
but if you'll just give me a chance to explain...
我会的  不过要先等我
I will, just as soon as
把这可爱的水晶纸镇还给你
I return this darling crystal paperweight.
住手
Stop it!
你不能跑到这里来毁了我的家
You can't come in here and destroy my home.
为什么不能
Why not?
你已经毁了我的生活
You destroyed my life.
如果我们不能理智地谈谈这事
If we can't talk about this rationally,
我就报警
I will call the police.
尽管报吧  我要走了
Go ahead, I'm leaving.
我倒是想说以后在乡村俱乐部见
You know, I would say that I'll see you at the country club,
但是  你也知道...
but, you know...
是你干的
It was you.
让你被投出去了吗
Who got you voted out?
没错
Yes.
理事会一知道卡尔患上了致命的传染病
The board didn't need much persuading once they knew
不需要怎么劝就同意了
that Karl was spreading a deadly disease.
我们当着所有朋友的面  被无礼地赶出来了
We were unceremoniously ejected in front of all of our friends.
希望你这下满意了
I hope you're satisfied.
满意
Satisfied?
你勾引了我的孩子
You seduced my child.
你真以为只是把你赶出乡村俱乐部
Do you honestly think that I would be satisfied
我就会满意了吗
just getting you kicked out of a country club?
我才刚开始呢  贱人
I am just getting started, bitch.
在我彻底收手前  我会彻底毁掉你
And before I am done, I will burn you,
毁掉你的生意
your business,
把这装修得丑哭的狗屎窝夷为平地
and this poorly decorated shithole to the ground!
满意了吗
Satisfied?
这里发生了什么
What the hell happened here?
情况刚刚变得更糟了
Things just got worse.
抱歉打扰
Sorry to intrude.
不知道你能不能借我一杯糖
I was wondering if I could borrow a cup of sugar.
我在烤蛋糕  忘了检查食品柜里的材料了
I'm baking a cake, and I forgot to check my pantry.
你并不是真的需要一杯糖  对吧
You don't really need a cup of sugar, do you?
是的
No.
进来吧
Come on in.
我能问问发生了什么事吗
Can I ask what happened?
我们去了一家百货商店
We were at a department store,
那个销售人员认出了我
and the sales clerk recognized me.
原来他是比我低两届的高中学弟
It turns out that he'd gone to my high school two years after I did,
所以他认识很多我的老朋友
so he knew a lot of my old friends.
我们就聊了五分钟
We only spoke for five minutes.
我们回来以后
After we got back,
拉尔夫指责我试图勾引那个男人
Ralph accused me of trying to seduce the man.
就这原因吗
That's why?
他以为你在调情
He thought you were flirting?
他只要一嫉妒  就会打我
He gets jealous. He can't help it.
我不明白
I don't understand
你怎么受得了这种日子
how you can live like this.
你一定过得不开心
You can't possibly be happy.
我是不开心
I'm not.
那你为什么不离开他呢
So why don't you leave?
我也可以问你同样的问题
I could ask you the same question.
什么意思
What?
你丈夫难道没有在外偷腥吗
Isn't your husband cheating on you?
他确实有
He is.
我有预感你早就知道
I had a feeling you knew.
那你为什么不离开他呢
So why don't you leave him?
我的情况和你的完全不一样
It's an entirely different situation.
他这是在羞辱你
He's humiliating you.
那一定很不好受
That's got to hurt.
确实如此
It does.
你还会再次相信他吗
Will you ever trust him again?
不会了
No.
如果你离开罗伯
And if you did leave Rob,
他会企图杀你吗
would he try and kill you?
当然不会
Of course not.
我丈夫会的
Well, my husband would.
他喜欢拿床头柜抽屉里上了膛的枪威胁我
He likes to threaten me with a loaded gun he keeps in his bedside drawer.
所以我选择留下
So I stay.
而你的借口又是什么呢
What in God's name is your excuse?
我总是期望着奇迹会发生
I keep hoping for a miracle.
奢望终有一天一切都会改变
That one day everything will change.
我们俩应该做朋友
You and I should be friends.
我们有很多相似之处
We have a lot in common.
艾琳・塔巴切尼克来自俄亥俄州
Irene Tabatchnick is from Ohio.
到她十六岁时
By the time she was 16,
她已被三个寄养家庭赶出家门
she was thrown out of three foster homes.
前两次  艾琳因偷钱被抓了现行
The first two times, Irene had been caught stealing cash.
那又如何  她那时还小  不懂事
So what? She was young. She was a kid.
她第三次被寄养家庭赶出来
She was kicked out of her third home
是因为她的养母指责她试图勾引她的丈夫
because her foster mother accused her of trying to seduce her husband.
也许那女人不想承认是她丈夫图谋不轨
Maybe the woman was in denial about what her husband was up to.
真相已无从知晓
Oh, we'll never know.
一周后  那所房子被烧毁
A week later, that house burned down.
被烧毁
Burned down?
她的养父母都葬身火海  伊莱
Those foster parents died, Eli.
艾琳・塔巴切尼克也人间蒸发
And Irene Tabatchnick just disappeared.
你觉得她...
So, what, you think she...?
虽然我们没有任何证据
I mean, we can't prove anything,
但是俄亥俄警方一直在找她
but the cops in Ohio are dying to talk to her.
这...这真是太扯了
Th-This is just so stupid.
这真是...洁德不会...
This is-- There's no way that Jade...
她的真名叫艾琳
Her name is Irene.
管她叫什么
Whatever.
她爱我们
She loves us.
如果她爱你  她会不断给你可卡因吗
If she loved you, would she keep giving you cocaine?
顺便说一句  你的脸色差极了
You look terrible, by the way.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you.
清醒点吧  伊莱
Come on, Eli.
她使你吸毒成瘾  好来利用你
She keeps you high so she can take advantage of you.
好让你继续允许她住在我们家
So that you let her live in our house,
好让你给她买新车
so that you buy her a new car.
你不必设套来跟我说这些  泰勒
You know, you didn't need to trick me to have this conversation, Taylor.
你打个电话不就完了
You could've just called.
我打给你了啊  不停地打
I did call. Every hour.
你在说什么  你从未打给我
What are you talking about? You never called me.
我很确定我打过
I most certainly did.
看  你看
Look. Look.
没有未接来电  也没有语音留言
No missed calls. No voice mails.
那个狡猾的婊子屏蔽了我的号码
That sneaky bitch blocked my number.
从我的手机上吗
On my phone?
她又不知道我的锁屏密码  怎么做到的
She couldn't do that without my pass code.
她知道你的锁屏密码
Well, she has your pass code.
她怎么会知道
How does she have that?
我告诉她的
I gave it to her.
这样你就可以卷走我的钱
So you could take away my money.
-以防你再拿去买毒品  -天呐
- To keep you from buying drugs. - Jesus.
你猜怎么着  也许她确实利用了我
You know what, maybe she does take advantage of me,
但至少她给了我自信
but at least she builds me up.
她不会让我感觉自己像个
She doesn't make me feel like a fuck-up
注定会一败涂地的废物
who's just destined to crash and burn.
我认为你会一败涂地的唯一原因
The only reason why I think you're gonna crash and burn,
伊莱  是因为你曾经那么干过
Eli, is because you've done it before.
你不知道我下班回家后
You have no idea what it feels like to come home from work
看到你倒在厨房地板上抽搐时我是什么感受
and then find you convulsing on the kitchen floor.
还得叫救护车  过了好久才来
And then to call the ambulance, which took forever.
我不会再那么做了  伊莱  我...
I'm not gonna do that again, Eli. I'm...
又没人求着你要那么做
No one is asking you to.
我不需要你的帮助
I don't need your help.
我的事业已经回春  我活得很好
I've got my career back. I'm fine.
这里唯一有毛病的人是你
The only one here with a problem is you.
你是个瘾君子  伊莱
You're an addict, Eli.
你得去戒毒所  你也心知肚明
You need to go to rehab, and you know it.
我只知道  泰勒
The only thing I know, Taylor,
我们之间已经没什么好谈的了
is that this conversation is over.
-伊莱  请不要走...  -别说了
- Eli, please stop... - Stop!
够了  让我走吧
Enough! Let me go.
-你很喜欢你的新皮球  对吗  -是的
- You like your new ball, don't you? - Yes.
晚餐后  我们要给莉迪亚姨妈写封感谢信
After dinner, we're going to write a thank you note to Aunt Lydia.
我不会写字
I don't know how to write.
我来写正文
I'll do the writing.
你可以在我们的名字旁边画一颗大大的爱心
You can draw a big heart right next to our names.
哎呀  你爸爸忘记把垃圾桶拿进来了
Oh dear, your father forgot to bring in the trash can.
你在这里玩一会儿  我去去就回
Play here for a second. I'll be right back.
快来  艾米莉
Come along, Emily.
你难道不想给爸爸看看你的新球吗
Don't you want to show your daddy your new ball?
想啊
Yes.
你们好啊
Hey there.
你们怎么回来啦
What are you two doing home?
我以为你们一小时后才会到家
I didn't expect you back for another hour.
莉迪亚姨妈身体抱恙
Aunt Lydia wasn't feeling well.
我们不得不缩短拜访时间
We had to cut our visit short.
-小公主  你手里拿的是什么  -皮球
- Hey, princess, what do you got there? - A ball.
莉迪亚姨妈送我的生日礼物
Aunt Lydia gave it to me for my birthday.
她的生日已经过去两个月了
Her birthday was two months ago.
心存感激  重在心意
Be nice. It's the thought that counts.
我能去玩了吗
Can I go play?
当然了
Of course you can.
罗伯  你掉了颗扣子吗
Rob, did you lose a button?
我刚在地上捡到一颗
I just found one on the floor.
我猜是的  谢谢
I guess I did. Thanks.
-妈妈  -抱歉  宝贝
- Mama. - I'm sorry, honey.
去吧
Here you go.
我晚餐要做芝士通心粉
I'm making mac and cheese for dinner,
所以别玩太久  好吗
so don't be too long, okay?
亲爱的
Honey?
打电话叫医生
Someone call a doctor.
艾米莉
Emily?
艾米莉  宝贝醒醒  睁开眼
Emily, honey, wake up. Open your eyes.
睁开眼啊  宝贝
Open your eyes, honey.
睁开眼啊
Open your eyes.
求你醒醒
Please wake up.
求你了...求你了...
Please... Please...
什么情况
What the hell?
谁开的车
Who was driving this car?!
她  她  她不知道从哪出来的
Sh-She, uh, she-she came out of nowhere,
先生  我发誓  我试着停车...
mister, I swear. I tried to stop...
你没关门吗
You left the gate open?
-关了  我确定我关了  -你确定吗
- No. I'm sure I locked it. - You're sure?
那艾米莉是怎么出去的
Then how did Emily get out of the backyard?
门闩离地有六英尺高
The latch is six feet off the ground!
我不知道  也许我忘了
I don't know. Maybe I forgot.
你没锁门
You didn't lock the gate.
You didn't lock the gate,
你还让她出去玩
and you let her out to play.
我得做晚餐啊
I had to make dinner.
这不是借口
That's no excuse.
我们的宝贝死了
Our baby is dead.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我以为是锁了的
I thought it was locked.
艾米
Amy.
我刚接到娜奥米的电话  卡尔得艾滋病了吗
I just got a call from Naomi. Does Karl have AIDS?
你们怎么能瞒着我
How could you not tell me?
我们以为还有时间
Well, we thought we had time.
你也能看出来  我还很健康呢
I mean, as you can see, I'm not exactly at death's door.
他的医生是最好的  所以别担心了
He has all the best doctors, so don't worry.
卡尔绝对可以参加你婚礼的
Karl will absolutely be able to walk you down the aisle.
这个时候  我都不确定婚礼还要不要办了
At this point, I'm not even sure there will be a wedding.
什么
What?
娜奥米打电话给了我们所有的朋友
Naomi's called all of our friends
告诉他们卡尔病了
and told them Karl is sick.
大家都不准备来了
People have been canceling right and left.
天啊
Oh, Lord.
如果没人来  还结什么婚
And if nobody's coming, why bother?
真是抱歉  亲爱的  我们能帮什么忙吗
Oh, I'm so sorry, my darling. Is there anything we can do?
这个嘛...
Well...
如果你不去的话我们也许还能挽回一下局面
we might be able to salvage this thing if you didn't come.
不去婚礼吗
To the wedding?
我理解
I understand.
没问题  我会待在家里
of course, I will stay home.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不行  卡尔必须去参加婚礼
No. Karl has to be at the wedding.
不然谁带你走红毯啊
Who's gonna walk you down the aisle?
你可以啊
You can do it.
我花六千美元买一条阿玛尼的礼服
I did not spend $6,000 on an Armani dress
-不是为了让它与人共行的  -好了  别吵
- just to give it a shared entrance. - Okay, let's not argue.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不介意
I don't mind.
不行
No!
我们是一家人
We are a family.
当坏事来临时我们应该互相支持
When bad things happen, we're supposed to support each other.
在我看来
The way I see it,
他不来参加就是在支持我
he is supporting me by staying away.
我要去给宾客们打电话告诉他们可以来了
I have to call my guests and tell them it's safe to come.
艾米  请三思啊
Amy, think of what you're doing.
你为了几个胆小的歧视者
You're choosing a few cowardly bigots
而放弃了养育你的人
over the man who raised you.
我是新娘
I'm the bride.
那是我的大喜日子  我希望能完美
It's my day, and I want it to be perfect.
如果卡尔致命的疾病
I am sorry if Karl's deadly illness
使你的婚礼失色不少  那么我很抱歉
is scraping some of the glitter off of your event,
但面对现实吧  这不会是你最后一场婚礼的
but let's face it, this won't be your last wedding.
-你够毒  -更重要的是
- Nice. - More importantly,
如果卡尔不去  我也不去
if Karl can't attend, I won't either.
-萨蒙妮  -行
- Oh, Simone. - Fine.
待在家吧  省得给我丢脸
Stay home. You'll save me some embarrassment.
大家议论的不只是卡尔
Karl's not the only one everybody's talking about.
我女儿是个怪物
My daughter is a monster.
她是新娘  两者没区别
Well, she's a bride. It's basically the same thing.
那么...会议怎么样
So... how'd the meeting go?
我想知道一切
I want to hear everything.
只能说斯科塞斯不会导演我的电影了
Well, let's just say that Scorsese's not gonna be directing my movie.
不会吧
Oh, no.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
但至少他喜欢这个剧本  对吧
But at least he loved the script, right?
-是的  是的  -很好
- He did. Yeah. - Good.
对  对  他特别喜欢
Yeah. Yeah, he especially liked the part
伊娃烧掉毒贩房子的那部分
where Eva burns the drug dealer's house down.
他喜欢那部分呀
He liked that?
对
Yeah.
对  他可喜欢了  他还问我是怎么想出来的
Yeah, he liked it so much, he asked me how I came up with it,
然后你懂的  我当然得告诉他那是你的点子
and, you know, of course I had to tell him it was your idea.
你不必给我功劳的
You didn't have to give me credit.
这个...
Yeah, well...
顺便问一下你是怎么想出来的
How did you come up with that, by the way?
就这么想出来的
Uh, it just came to me.
就突然想出来的吗
Just out of the blue?
对
Yeah.
因为这想法太不寻常了  你知道吗
'Cause it-it's such an unusual concept, you know,
以纵火来报复
arson as a form of revenge.
你也不知道你是怎么想出来的
You have no idea how that came to you?
这有什么重要的
Why does it matter?
我  我只是好奇
I-I'm-I'm just curious.
我不知道  就突然想到的
I don't know-- it just popped into my head.
就嘣的一下
Just, boop?
嘣的一下  没错
Boop. Yeah.
有时候就是这样
Sometimes that happens.
洁德这个名字也是这么来的吗
Is that how you came up with the name Jade?
就突然想到的吗
It just popped into your head?
什么
What?
我承认  这名字比艾琳更适合你
It suits you better than Irene, I'll give you that.
你最近跟谁说话了
Who have you been talking to?
看路
Hey, watch the road.
伊莱  别逗我
Eli, do not fuck with me.
不然要怎么样  烧掉我房子吗
Or else what, you're gonna burn down my house?
你跟杜克谈过了
You talked to Duke?
天呐  你干了那些事
Oh, my God. You did those things.
干了什么  他说了我什么
Did what? What did he say about me?
我的天  你杀了那些人  我的天
Oh, my God, you killed those people. Oh, my God.
伊莱  那人是骗子
Eli, Eli, the man is a liar!
-慢点  慢点  -伊莱  他说的一个字
- All right, slow down, slow down. - Eli, you can't believe
-你都不能信  -老天  看着点
- a fucking word he says! - Jesus, watch out!
卡尔  已经11点过了
Karl, it's after 11:00.
你什么时候去画廊
When are you going to the gallery?
当人们不再认为
When people stop assuming
可以通过石版画感染上艾滋的时候
you can catch AIDS from a lithograph.
他们全都可以去死了
Oh, screw them all.
我们要去亨廷顿吃午餐吗
Shall we have lunch at the Huntington?
-你请客的话  -很好
- Well, if you're paying. - Good.
我不想再一下午都盯着这些墙了
I can't spend another afternoon staring at these walls.
我也是
Oh, I can't either.
我们当初是怎么想的  全弄成了紫色
What were we thinking with all the damn purple?
-是我的幻觉还是  -不
- Is it just my imagination or...? - No.
不  他们在盯着我们
No. They're staring at us.
我们又做了什么
What have we done now?
去死吧  艾滋病基佬
我的天
Oh, my God.
去死吧  艾滋病基佬
什么
Wha...
有人看到是谁喷的吗
Did anyone see who did this?
肯定有人看到了
Someone had to have seen something.
别呆呆地看着  回答我
Don't just gawk. Answer me!
-萨蒙妮  -卡尔
- Simone. - Karl!
我有点晕  我得回屋躺下
I'm-I'm a little dizzy. I just need to go inside and lie down.
你得去看医生  你能走到车上去吗
You need to see a doctor. Can you make it to the car?
有人能帮帮我们吗
Can someone please help us?
拜托帮我扶他上车
Please help us to the car!
得艾滋的人是他吗
Is he the one with AIDS?
谁在乎  他是人啊
Who cares? He's a human being!
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
我很感激
You know, I'm so grateful.
我想雇你来我们家工作
I want to hire you to work on our property.
亲爱的  他为我们工作了六年了
Darling, he's worked for us for six years.
当然  非常感谢
Oh, of course. Um, thank you very much, uh...
-胡里奥  -对
- Julio. - Right.
胡里奥  上去吧
Julio. Here you go.
该死  该死
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
我得走了
I have to go.
什么
What?
天  我好想你
God, I missed you.
我想念和你做爱
I missed this.
我也是
Mmm, me, too.
我度过了有趣的一天
So, I had an interesting day.
是吗
Yeah?
我跟波特先生谈了  夜店的老板
I talked to Mr. Porter, that fella who runs the nightclub,
我跟他说了怀孕的事
I told him about the baby.
他说了什么
What did he have to say?
他祝贺了我
Well, he said congratulations.
他还说  一旦我生下孩子后
He also said, once I have the baby,
他希望我能立刻回去表演
he wants me right back up on that stage.
是不是很棒
Isn't that terrific?
是的
Yeah.
我就知道你会这么想
I knew you would think so.
可现在谈这个是不是过早了点
But isn't it a little early to talk about this?
先等孩子生下来再做决定吧
Why don't we see how you feel after the baby arrives?
我的感觉不会变
I won't feel any different.
照顾孩子很辛苦的
Well, taking care of a baby is hard work.
你也许会太累无法继续唱歌
You might be too tired to keep singing.
唱歌我永远不会累
I'll never be too tired to sing.
到时看吧
We'll see.
罗伯
Rob...
这是我的梦想
It's my dream.
梦想很棒
And dreams are great,
但你也要现实点
but you have to be realistic.
唱歌那行不是那么容易混的
It's a tough business to break into.
我知道
I know.
我家贝丝・安当初也想进入演艺界
My Beth Ann wanted to be in show business,
她最后终于想明白  放弃了
and she finally came to her senses and gave it up.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
也许我比她更有天赋
Well, maybe I'm more talented than she is.
她其实很不错  她想弹钢琴
She wasn't half-bad. She wanted to play piano.
钢琴
Piano?
对  她想成为钢琴演奏家  太荒谬了
Yeah, she wanted to be a concert pianist, which is ridiculous.
不过你想做什么都行
But you do what you want.
只要我回家后桌上有热腾腾的饭菜
As long as dinner's on the table when I get home,
我又在乎什么呢
what do I care?
说来有趣
You know, it's kind of funny.
我朋友希拉也想当钢琴演奏家
Uh, my friend Sheila also wanted to be a concert pianist.
是吗  世界真小
Yeah? Small world.
我得走了
Well, I got to go.
今晚给你打电话
I'll call you tonight.
格罗夫夫人
Mrs. Grove?
请说
Yes?
根据初步检测
Based on the initial exam,
我们认为你丈夫可能是患上了杰氏肺囊虫肺炎
we think your husband probably has Pneumocystis pneumonia,
这病在免疫系统受损的人群中很常见
an infection common in men with suppressed immune systems.
有多严重
How serious is it?
大多数病人经过治疗可以康复
Most patients recover with treatment.
大多数  你是说有的不能吗
"Most"? Do you mean some don't?
我们还会做一些检测  然后可以知道更多
We're gonna run some tests, then we'll know more.
谢谢
Thank you.
娜奥米
Naomi.
-护士  放下手中的活  叫保安  -不用了
- Nurse, put that down and call security. - Don't bother.
我就说一件事  然后就走
I just have one thing to say and then I'll go.
如果你觉得我会让你靠近我孩子
If you think I'm gonna let you go anywhere near my child...
我不是来找汤米的  我是来道歉的
I'm not here for Tommy. I'm here to apologize.
道歉  现在
An apology? Now?
-当我没兴趣吧  -那就告诉我
- Color me disinterested. - Then just tell me
我得做什么才能让你放过卡尔
what I have to do to get you to leave Karl alone.
我对他什么都没做
I haven't done anything to him.
你的蜚短流长使他成了过街老鼠
You have spread your poison and made him a pariah.
他失去了朋友
He has lost friends,
被女儿的婚礼拒之门外
been banned from his daughter's wedding,
他的家被糟蹋
had his home vandalized.
天呐  他病了  他不该沦落到
God, he's sick. He does not deserve
在丑闻和耻辱中等死
to spend his last days hounded by scandal and shame.
或许如此  但如果卡尔被无辜牵连
Maybe he doesn't, but if Karl's caught in the crossfire,
那也是因为他离你太近了
it's only because he's been standing too close to you.
娜奥米  我求你了
Naomi, I am begging.
责怪我  毁灭我
Blame me, destroy me.
我保证不会还手
I promise I won't fight back.
但求你别把卡尔扯进来
But please leave Karl out of it.
妈
Mom.
你干了什么好事
What have you done?
伊莱
Eli.
你是他妻子吗
Are you his wife?
是的
Yeah.
他没事吧  为什么昏迷了
Is he okay? Why-- why is he unconscious?
我们必须给他用镇静剂
He needed to be sedated.
他的肋骨骨折了  不过会康复的
His ribs are fractured, but he'll recover.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我们给他注射前  他说想见你
Before we put him out, he was asking for you.
我们告诉他你马上就来
We told him you were on your way.
我尽快赶来了
I came as fast as I could.
他给你写了留言
He wrote you this note.
说这很重要
Said it was important.
戒毒
一切都还好吗
Everything okay?
嗯  都会好起来的
Yeah. I think it will be.
他要过一阵子才能醒过来
It's gonna be a while before he wakes up.
我会守在他身边等他醒来
Well, I'm gonna be here when he does.
斯坦顿夫人
Mrs. Stanton.
你好  克莱尔
Hello, Claire.
我有事找罗伯
I need to speak to Rob.
他不在
He's not here.
他什么时候才回来
How long until he returns?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
你要去旅行吗
Are you going on a trip?
我要回堪萨斯州的老家
I'm going back home to Kansas.
-去探亲吗  -不是
- For a visit? - No.
我要离开罗伯
I'm leaving Rob.
他有外遇了
He's been having an affair.
他不知道我知道了
He doesn't know I know,
所以我想我应该亲自告诉他
and I thought I should tell him in person.
斯坦顿夫人  我很遗憾
Oh, Mrs. Stanton, I'm so sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道他可能在哪里吗
Do you have any idea where he might be?
他在她的公寓
He's at her apartment.
这么说你早就知道
So you've known about this.
你要是早告诉我就好了
I wish you had told me.
我还以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
我没做过你的朋友
I haven't been your friend,
一秒钟都没做过
not for one second.
而你应该恨我
And you should hate me
因为我对你所做的一切
for everything I've done to you.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
罗伯已经背着你出轨很多年了
Rob's been cheating on you for years...
有过各种各样的女人
with all sorts of women.
我就是其中之一
And I was one of them.
我是在保护你
I was protecting you.
通过毁掉他们的生活吗
By destroying their lives?
她占了你的便宜
She took advantage of you.
不  是我追求了她
No. I pursued her.
而且我们的感情是真爱
And what we had, it was real.
你这么想是因为她扭曲了你的思想
You only think that because she twisted your mind.
相信我  没有她你会过得更好
Trust me, you are better off without her.
不  也许没有你我会过得更好
No, maybe I'd be better off without you.
汤米
Tommy...
爸总是说你报复心很重
Dad always said that you were vindictive,
我一有机会就应该离开你
and I should get away from you as soon as I got the chance.
你爸是个可悲的酒鬼
Your dad was a pathetic drunk.
但他清楚你的底细
But he had your number.
我今晚就走
I'm leaving tonight.
明天早上乘第一班飞机去欧洲
And I'll be on the first plane to Europe in the morning.
你以为我会出钱让你去欧洲游荡吗
Well, you think I'm just gonna pay for you to go traipsing around Europe?
我18岁了  可以动用我的信托基金
I'm 18. I have access to my trust fund.
我不需要你的任何东西
I don't need anything from you.
但我还是你妈妈
I am still your mother.
不  从现在起  你只是我曾认识的一个女人
No, from now on, you're just some lady that I used to know.
二号楼梯
医院入口
你要开走吗
You pulling out?
先不走
Not yet.
我在等人
I'm waiting for someone.
你一定要理解  多年来我一直
You have to understand, I have wanted to tell you
想告诉你  但是...
for years, but...
天呐  我真羞愧
Oh, God, I am so ashamed.
我要离开他了  克莱尔
I'm leaving him, Claire.
已经无所谓了
It doesn't matter anymore.
等我把剩下的话说完  你就不会这么想了
You won't feel that way once I've told you the rest.
还有别的要说的
There's something else?
我最后一次和你丈夫上床
The last time I slept with your husband...
是在你孩子死的那天
was the day your child died.
当时我们在你们以前的房子的卧室里
We were in your bedroom at your old house...
罗伯听到了关车门的声音
when Rob heard a car door slam.
他起床看到你和你女儿
He got up to see you and your daughter
提前回家了
had come home early.
他吆喝我赶紧穿衣服
He yelled at me to get dressed.
你开始往后院拖垃圾桶
You began dragging a trash can to the backyard,
所以我们有时间跑到楼下
so we had time to run downstairs.
我本来想躲在壁橱里
I was going to hide in a closet,
但罗伯说太冒险了
but Rob said it was too dangerous.
他让我从房子侧门出去
So he told me to get out through the side of the house.
你们从前门进来的时候
So while you were coming in the front door...
你们好啊
Hey there.
我绕着房子跑出去
I ran around the side of the house...
从后院的大门离开了
and left through the gate.
我没关门
And I left it open.
几小时后  一个同事打来电话
A few hours later, someone from work called.
他们告诉我发生了什么
They told me what had happened,
我瞬间就知道是我的错
and I instantly knew it was my fault.
斯坦顿夫人
Oh, Mrs. Stanton,
我不知该如何表达我有多抱歉
I can't even begin to tell you how sorry I am.
我有一个问题
I have one question.
什么
What's that?
罗伯知道你没有关门吗
Did Rob know you had not closed the gate?
我那晚跟他打了电话  告诉了他
I called him that night and I told him.
他说他可以原谅我
And he said he could forgive me...
如果我不告诉任何人发生了什么
if I never told anyone else what had happened.
于是我没有说出去
And I didn't.
我很惭愧
I was so ashamed.
我知道你不能原谅我的所作所为
I know you can't forgive me for what I've done,
但我愿意下半辈子
but I will spend the rest of my life
都用来弥补我的过错
trying to atone for what I did to you.
起来
Get up.
你做了  一件很可怕的事  克莱尔
You did... a horrible thing, Claire.
但我会原谅你
But I'll forgive you
如果你答应为我做一件事
if you promise to do one thing for me.
任何事都行
Anything.
你不能告诉任何人
You will never tell another living soul
我们有过这次对话
that we had this conversation.
什么
What?
罗伯不能知道
Rob can't know.
我决定不离开他了
I've decided not to leave him.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你不需要
You don't have to.
你只需要许下庄严誓约
All you need to do is give me your solemn vow.
做到后  我就原谅你
Do that and you have my forgiveness.
好
Okay.
我答应你
I promise.
谢谢你  克莱尔
Thank you, Claire.
乖乖
Hey, girl,
你怎么来了
what are you doing here?
它想你了
She missed you.
洁德
Jade.
希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.
我自己进来的  你的锁坏了
I let myself in. Your lock's busted.
为什么我觉得是你弄坏的
Why do I get the feeling that you busted it?
别生气  我想见你
Don't be mad. I wanted to see you.
好打断我另一条腿吗
Why, so you could break my other leg?
天  我很抱歉
Oh, God, I'm so sorry about that.
上次局势有点失控
Things got a little crazy last time,
但我想补偿你
but I'm trying to make it up to you.
你打扫了房间
See you cleaned a little bit.
有点像猪圈  不是我挑剔
It was kind of a pigsty. Not that I'm being critical.
我知道你最近
I know you've been busy with, um,
在监狱里
jail and stuff.
-你在做饭  -是的  锅烤肉
- And you're cooking? - Yeah, pot roast.
用的你喜欢的那个食谱
The recipe you like.
你怎么不给你豪宅里的
Why aren't you cooking for your rich friends
富人朋友做
in their fancy mansion?
他们把你赶出来了吗
Did they kick you out?
伊莱知道了我的过去
Eli found out about my past,
所以我收拾了东西走了
so I packed up my stuff and I left.
真可惜
What a shame.
你跟他说了话吗
Did you talk to him?
你为什么会这么想
Now, why would you think that?
因为只有你知道我真名
Because you're the only one who knows my real name.
我对天发誓  我没有告诉伊莱
Hand to God, I did not tell Eli.
你告诉了其他人吗
Did you tell someone else?
泰勒来监狱看了我
Taylor came to see me in jail.
该死
Oh, shit!
她说如果我打你小报告
Yeah, she offered to pay my bail
她就愿意支付我的保释金
if I ratted you out, so...
泰勒是律师
Taylor is a lawyer!
她有人脉  警察仍然在找我
She knows people, and the cops are still looking for me.
我可能会进监狱的
I could end up in prison!
我也许还要拄一年的拐杖
Yeah, and I may be walking with a cane for a year,
我想我们扯平了
so I guess we're even.
我得离开这里  我需要钱
I got to get out of town. I need money.
-别看我  我身无分文  -你肯定有点什么
- Don't look at me, I'm busted. - Well, you must have something.
你爷爷的表呢
Like, what about your grandfather's watch?
-怎么了  -给我  我去当掉
- What about it? - Give it to me! I'll pawn it.
想得美
The hell you will!
该死  杜克  你欠我的
Goddamn it, Duke! You owe it to me!
你这次把我害惨了
You really fucked me this time!
我屁都不欠你  滚出我家
I don't owe you shit. Now get the fuck out of my house!
离我远点
You stay away from me.
又开始瞪眼了吗
Again with the crazy eyes, huh?
听着  宝贝  把刀放下
Look, baby, just put the knife down, okay?
把刀...
Just put the knife...
你要为此付出代价的
You're gonna pay for that.
你觉得吗
You think?
下午好  有什么需要帮助的
Afternoon. What can I do for you?
我要买把枪
I need to buy a gun.